atlusonline.com 2012-01-02

# Privacy Policy - Atlus Online - Play for Free Online MMORPGs, Fantasy Steampunk Game To Play Online, Streaming Anime, Oekaki Wall

_**Atlus Online Privacy Policy**_

By using this Website, you signify your assent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use this site. This Privacy Policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically to ensure that you are aware of any changes. If we make a material change to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting the change on this website or in this Privacy Policy and, if necessary, give you additional choices regarding such change. Your continued use of the Atlus Online website will signify your acceptance of these changes.

Updated as of February 2, 2009

_Welcome to Atlus Online!_

**Our Privacy Commitment**

Atlus U.S.A., Inc., and its subsidiaries and affiliates (collectively, "Atlus”) respects the privacy rights of its online visitors and recognizes the importance of protecting all information that you may choose to share with us. To further this commitment, we adopted this Online Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy”) to guide how we collect, store, and use the information you provide us.

**What information does this Privacy Policy cover?**

This Privacy Policy applies only to personal information collected on the websites where this Privacy Policy is posted, and does not apply to any other information collected by Atlus through any other means.

This Privacy Policy applies to the collection, use, and sharing of personal information collected as of the date that this Privacy Policy is posted.

This Privacy Policy applies only to information submitted and collected online, and does not apply to information that may be collected by Atlus offline.

This Privacy Policy applies only to websites maintained by Atlus, and not to our international affiliates, or any websites maintained by other entities to which we link. Atlus is therefore not responsible for the content or activities provided on those websites.

Finally, the terms of this Privacy Policy are subject to all applicable laws.

**What types of personal information do we collect about our guests?**

We don't require personal information to access our website. But if you prefer not to disclose personal information, you may not be able to enjoy certain features of our website. Personal information is information that identifies you and may be used to contact you.

**INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE TO US**

We will collect personal information from you when you use certain features on our website. For example, we collect personal information to: 1. register for our website 2. subscribe to our newsletter 3. participate in polls, surveys and questionnaires 4. participate in contests, sweepstakes, or other promotions 5. use e-cards, wish lists, and tell-a-friend features 6. register a product that you have purchased, or 7. receive customer or technical support.

Typically, this information includes: 1. name 2. e-mail address 3. telephone number 4. shipping and billing address, and 5. for those purchasing products online, credit card information.

Additionally, we may also collect other types of information (known as demographic information) such as your age or date of birth, gender, hobbies, occupation, platform preferences, and other game ownership information. This demographic information may be associated with your personal information.

**INFORMATION COLLECTED THROUGH TECHNOLOGY**

We collect information through technology to make our websites more interesting and secure. For example, when you come to one of our websites, we collect your IP address. An IP address is often associated with the portal through which you enter the Internet, like your ISP (Internet Service Provider), your company, or your university. Standing alone, your IP address is not personally identifiable. At times, we also use IP addresses to collect information regarding the frequency with which our guests visit various parts of our websites. We may combine this information with your personal information.

**COOKIES AND WEB BEACONS**

Our websites also use cookies and web beacons to collect and store personal information.

Cookies are pieces of information that a website sends to your computer while you are viewing the website. We use cookies for a variety of purposes. For example, when you return to one of our websites after logging in, cookies provide information to the website so that the website will remember who you are. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You can do this through your browser (like Mozilla Firefox or Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your web experience smoother, like the features mentioned above, and some of our services may not function properly.

Web beacons are small pieces of data that are embedded in images on the pages of websites and in our email communications. We also use these web beacons to analyze the traffic patterns, such as the frequency users visit various areas of our websites. These technical methods may involve transmitting information either directly to us or to another entity authorized by us to collect information on our behalf. We also use web beacons in HTML e-mails that we send our guests to determine whether our guests have opened those e-mails or clicked on links in those e-mails.

**NETWORK ADVERTISERS**

Advertisements that are managed by third parties may be placed on our website. These companies are called "network advertisers.” Network advertisers who may place advertisements on our websites may also use cookies and web beacons to collect non-personal information when you click on or move your cursor over one of their banner advertisements. You may not realize this information is being collected. In some cases, we may have access to information from web beacons and cookies used by network advertisers on our sites and this information may permit us to identify other sites that you have visited that are also associated with the network advertiser.

Further, once you've clicked on an advertisement or third party logo and have left our websites, our Privacy Policy no longer applies and you must read the privacy policy of the advertiser to see how your personal information will be handled on their website.

Finally, please be aware that advertisers or websites with links to our sites may collect personal information about you. And remember, this Privacy Policy does not apply to, and cannot control the activities of, those other advertisers or websites.

How is your personal information used and shared?

Whatever the purpose may be, we will only collect information to the extent reasonably necessary to fulfill your requests and our legitimate business objectives.

**ATLUS' ACTIVITIES**

We use the personal information we collect to: 1. respond to your requests for information and newsletters, 2. provide you with product support and customer service, 3. determine if you are eligible to receive certain products or services, 4. provide you with additional information that may be of interest, including marketing materials, and 5. for other everyday business purposes, such as product development and website administration.

We don't share your personal information (e.g., e-mail address) with unaffiliated third parties to use for their direct marketing purposes.

**E-CARDS**

When you send an e-card, we delete both sender and recipient email address information after sending your e-card.

**FORUMS AND MESSAGE BOARDS**

If you register for access to our forums or message boards, we may use your personal information to enable you to view and post messages on the boards. You should understand, however, that community forums, blogs, and message boards are tools that allow you to communicate with members of the online community. So whenever you give out personal information in public areas, that information can be collected and used by people you don't know.

**SERVICE PROVIDERS**

We occasionally employ other companies to perform services necessary to our internal operations. For example, we may partner with other companies to personalize our web pages, analyze customers' interaction with our website, and process consumer surveys. We may also provide postal addresses to the U.S. Post Office or other couriers for delivery purposes. While providing services for us, these companies may access your personal information. Those companies storing or maintaining personal information for us have agreed to use secure methods.

**BUSINESS INFORMATION**

For practical reasons, we treat personal information submitted to us in a business capacity different from information we receive in a non-business capacity. Personal information submitted to us in a business capacity (e.g. resumes, event sponsorship, etc.) may be shared with third parties, depending on the nature of the inquiry.

**PURCHASE OR SALE OF BUSINESS**

From time to time, we may purchase a business or sell one or more of our businesses and your personal information may be transferred as a part of the purchase or sale. If we purchase a business, the personal information received with that business would be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy, if it is practicable and permissible to do so. If we sell a business, we will include provisions in the selling contract requiring the purchaser to treat your personal information in the same way required by this Privacy Policy (including any amendments to this Privacy Policy). The provisions of this paragraph will also apply if we are sold as part of bankruptcy proceedings.

**DISCLOSURES REQUIRED BY LAW AND DISCLOSURES TO HELP PROTECT THE SECURITY AND SAFETY OF OUR WEBSITES AND OTHERS**

Please note that we may disclose any information as permitted or required by law, when we believe in good faith it is necessary for safety purposes, required for legal reporting, or to protect our legal rights or enforce our Terms of Service or any contest rules. We may also disclose information about you to our auditors or legal advisors, or in response to a subpoena.

**AGGREGATE INFORMATION**

We may take your personal information and make it non-personally identifiable. We do this either by combining it with information about other individuals (aggregating your information with information about other individuals), and by removing characteristics (e.g., your name) that make the information personally identifiable to you. This process is known as de-personalizing your information. We may use de-personalized information in any way and share it with third parties.

_What choices do you have about the collection, use and sharing of your personal information?_

Atlus allows you to control the way that we use personal identifying information that we might obtain. At the time you provide personal information, Atlus may give you the option of declining any future offers or information about new products, promotions, or services. If you signed up to receive newsletters or other emails from us, many of the mailings have procedures within them to cancel the receipt of any future mailings. You can opt-out any time simply by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the message.

**YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**

Since 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits our customers who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. We do not share our customer's personal information with unaffiliated third parties for their own direct marketing purposes.

For inquires regarding our disclosure policy, please send us an e-mail to privacy@atlusonline.com.

_What kinds of security measures do we take to safeguard your personal information?_

The security and confidentiality of your information is extremely important to us. That's why we have technical, administrative, and physical security measures in place to protect your personal information from unauthorized access and improper use. We also review our security procedures periodically to consider appropriate new technology and updated methods. But, despite our reasonable efforts, no security measure is ever perfect or impenetrable.

_How can you update your personal information and profile?_

You may update or delete your personal information or modify your account preferences by accessing the "My Account” area of our website. If you wish to delete your e-mail address from our system, your account will also need to be deleted. You may also contact us directly with questions about your account at privacy@atlusonline.com.

_How can you ask questions, or send us comments, about this privacy policy?_

If you have questions or wish to send us comments about this Privacy Policy, please e-mail or contact us at:

privacy@atlusonline.com

Any personal information you provide to the above e-mail and postal mail addresses will not be used to send you promotional materials, unless you request it.

_How will you know if we amend this Privacy Policy?_

If you have questions or wish to send us comments about this Privacy Policy, please e-mail or contact us at:

privacy@atlusonline.com

Any personal information you provide to the above e-mail and postal mail addresses will not be used to send you promotional materials, unless you request it.

**Atlus' Kids Privacy Policy**

Last updated February 2, 2009

Atlus has developed its websites with the goal of creating an enjoyable experience for all users. This Kids Privacy Policy is designed to answer your questions regarding our privacy policies concerning children under the age of 13. Building on our general Privacy Policy, we recognize the need to provide additional privacy protections when children visit sites on which we post this Kids Privacy Policy. We explain those additional protections in this Kids Privacy Policy.

The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA”) requires that we inform parents and legal guardians about how we collect, use, and disclose personal information from children under 13 years of age. COPPA also requires us to obtain the consent of parents and guardians for children under 13 years of age to use certain features of our Web sites. Below we explain how we do that for children. Also, when we use the term "parent” below, we mean to include legal guardians.

_What types of information do we collect about kids?_

Kids can surf Atlus Online's sites, view content, and enjoy many features without having to disclose any personal information. We don't collect personal information from kids while they use our sites unless they register on Atlus Online's Official Forums.

For those who choose to register and participate in certain areas of our website, we collect personal information directly from kids to: 1. register for our Official Forum, or 2. participate in polls, surveys, and questionnaires on the Official Forum.

We may collect personal information from parents to allow kids to participate in certain activities offered on our websites and within our kids' subscription products. These activities may include purchasing product in one of our online stores, participating in games, reward programs, contests, sweepstakes, events or other promotions.

Typically, this information includes: 1. name 2. e-mail address 3. telephone number 4. shipping and billing address, and 5. for those purchasing products online, credit card information.

We may collect demographic information (e.g., date of birth, gender, and game preferences) and combine it with the child's personal information. Atlus Online will only collect this information if it is voluntarily and properly submitted to us by either the child or parent.

Note that all commercial sites directed to children under 13 are prohibited by U.S. law from conditioning a kid's participation in an online activity on the kid's providing more personal information than is reasonably necessary.

Some areas of our website may offer features like electronic postcards that allow kids to submit personal information (e.g., email address) without first disclosing their age or obtaining verifiable parental consent. These areas provide services in a way that doesn't require prior verifiable parental consent. Finally, we may collect demographic information about kids. For example, if a kid participates in a survey, we may collect those responses. Among them, we may collect age, gender, hobbies, and interests or other demographic information about gaming and preferences. We also use some passive technologies, including cookies and web beacons, to monitor traffic on our websites. This demographic information may be associated with a child's personal information.

_How do we use and share the personally identifiable information we collect about children?_

If a parent allows us to collect personal information about their child, we may link certain information collected through technology (see the "Information Collected Through Technology" section of our General Privacy Policy) to that personal information.

We may use the information that we collect from and about children for our business purposes, including record-keeping, transaction fulfillment, and marketing. The contact information gathered from a kid is used to obtain consent to our information collection from their parents.

Atlus Online may share kids' personal information with outside entities hired to assist with internal website support operations (e.g., online product fulfillment, email services, or technical support). These entities have agreed to maintain confidentiality, security, and integrity of all the personal information they obtain from us.

We do not share any information about a child with any third parties unless the disclosure is reasonably necessary to: 1. comply with law, including, for example, to comply with a court order or subpoena; 2. enforce our Terms of Service, or site or game/promotion rules; 3. in connection with the purchase or sale of assets, a merger, reorganization, bankruptcy, or similar corporate transaction; or 4. protect the safety and security of our Guests and our Websites.

_How do we notify and obtain consent from parents for the collection of personal information from their children?_

When a child under 13 attempts to register at our website, the child can download and print a parental consent form. Then, you, as the parent, can fill out and sign the parental consent form and mail or fax it back to us. If the parent ignores or refuses to register the child, we will delete all contact information from our database. If the parent permits the registration, the child will be granted access to the features described in the notification message.

_How can parents access, change or delete personally identifiable information about their children?_

At any time, a parent can contact our customer service department to access, change, or delete personal information we collected from his or her child by contacting us at:

privacy@atlusonline.com

Our representatives will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before disclosing your child's information.

_What kinds of security measures do we take to safeguard kids' personally identifiable information?_

We take the security and confidentiality of kids' information very seriously. We have implemented technical, administrative, and physical security measures to protect kids' personal information from unauthorized access and improper use. From time to time, we review our security procedures to consider appropriate new technology and methods. But please understand that, despite our best efforts, no security measure is perfect or impenetrable.

_How will we notify parents if our Kids Privacy Policy changes?_

At any time, we may amend our Kids Privacy Policy. We will send e-mail notice to parents of any material changes in the way we intend to collect, use, or share kids' personal information. At all times, parents should update their personal information to provide us current e-mail addresses. We will apply material changes in our Kids Privacy Policy only in conformance with applicable law, including any applicable provisions of COPPA that require parental consent.

_Who do guests contact with questions or concerns about our Kids Privacy Policy?_

If you have questions or wish to send us comments about this Privacy Policy, please e-mail or contact us at:

privacy@atlusonline.com

Any personal information you provide to the above e-mail and postal mail addresses will not be used to send you promotional materials, unless you request it.
